so what do you think I would have made
you happy if I finalized you, did
you ever think about the relationship of my family members, I
know, last
year we will see you, we were there earlier and also give you medicine
powder, so what did you
say now, those who take themselves
seriously about protecting themselves with foresight, do they
not care about their lives, so listen, if you ask some people if they are not
wearing a helmet, they say,
oh, an accident will happen after asking, how many times should you
tell me, these rules and regulations are not for our happiness,
for your Shetty, we
follow you, that you subscribe,
we are definitely police, but we cannot leave you,
how many times have people seen us, they say,
now this file will be filed, they have to complete the target,
a target of
and Yash is, a
target is, as we have to achieve
zero casualties, quickly come, the
hide and seek of life has become something new
and to escape from this, only muscles will
not work, wear them in the film also
because now we have to walk together in the journey from long gown to unlock